Thank you.
谢谢。
¶¶
¶¶
I love you.
我爱你。
Thank you.
谢谢。
All right, welcome back to the Ethereum Protocol Fellowship Study Group.
好的，欢迎回到以太坊协议研究小组。
We are on week eight now, and this is the development track session for week eight.
我们现在正在第八周，这是第八周的开发赛道。
We are here talking with Paul Harris from Tecku, who will give us a deep dive into the Ethereum consensus client architecture.
我们在这里与Tecku的Paul Harris交谈，Tecku将为我们深入了解以太坊共识客户架构。
So yeah, I'll pass it off to Mario, maybe give us a little bit more in-depth intro for Paul here, and then we'll kick it off.
是的，我会把它传给马里奥，也许在这里给我们保罗的深度介绍，然后将其拉开。
Hey, everyone.
嘿，大家。
First of all, Paul, thank you so much for joining us today.
首先，保罗，非常感谢您今天加入我们。
One thing you should know about Paul is that he's in Australia.
关于保罗，您应该知道的一件事是他在澳大利亚。
It's very early for him today, so really thank you so much for making it and joining us today here.
今天对他来说还很早，所以非常感谢您制作并在这里加入我们。
Because we're very eager to learn about the consensus layer and about the actual client architectures.
因为我们非常渴望了解共识层和实际客户端体系结构。
In previous weeks, we had an insight into the consensus layer, more abstract, from Alex Stokes.
在过去的几周中，我们对亚历克斯·斯托克斯（Alex Stokes）的共识层有深入的了解。
We saw the execution layer client, and today we'll finally also dive into the real code base of consensus client.
我们看到了执行层客户端，今天我们最终也深入研究了共识客户端的真实代码基础。
And specifically, Paul prepared for us a little presentation about how the EIP or an idea becomes a specification
特别是，保罗为我们准备了有关EIP或想法如何成为规范的一些演讲
and then it gets implemented through this process that we've been discussing through the study group before.
然后，它通过以前通过研究小组讨论的这一过程实施。
So yeah, we are really excited to learn about that.
是的，我们真的很高兴得知这一点。
Paul is working on the Consensus Client TeKu as part of Consensus campaign.
作为共识活动的一部分，保罗正在共识客户Teku。
And it's been a while, I believe Paul has been around Ethereum for a few years already.
而且已经有一段时间了，我相信保罗已经在以太坊周围已经存在了几年。
He's been also doing AMA for the protocol fellowship last year, a year ago, but it was
去年，他也一直在为协议奖学金做AMA，但这是
non-technical.
非技术。
We had a really nice chat there, but it wasn't really the deep dive, so yeah, excited to
我们在那里聊天非常好，但这不是真正的潜水，所以，是的，很兴奋
have that with you.
有你。
Yeah, the stage is yours.
是的，舞台是你的。
Feel free to share your screen and get us through it.
随时分享您的屏幕并通过它来完成它。
Thank you so much again for being here.
非常感谢您在这里。
Awesome.
惊人的。
Thanks very much for inviting me.
非常感谢您邀请我。
That sounds okay, I assume.
我认为这听起来还不错。
I'm just using headphones and I do tend to
我只是在使用耳机，我确实倾向于
be interesting sometimes on Zoom,
有时会变得有趣，
so I thought I'd check it.
所以我以为我会检查它。
Um, sounds great.
嗯，听起来很棒。
Awesome.
惊人的。
So, I'll share a screen.
所以，我将分享一个屏幕。
Sorry about the background.
对不起，背景。
Usually I have a,
通常我有一个
usually I hide the cupboard and everything.
通常我隐藏了橱柜和一切。
Is that my screen?
那是我的屏幕吗？
I've prepared a bit of a slide deck.
我已经准备了一些幻灯片甲板。
it's a bit more like not just me talking. As it's already been said, I work for, on
这不仅是我说话。正如已经说过的那样，我为
the consensus layer on a client called Tecku, and I do have to say that the views expressed
一个名为tecku的客户端上的共识层，我必须说表达的观点
are mine, and they do not necessarily reflect the views of ConsenSys.
是我的，它们不一定反映共识的观点。
Just a quick little bit about me, I'm a blockchain protocol engineer with ConsenSys, the company
关于我的一点点，我是与共识的区块链协议工程师，该公司
ConsenSys, and I work on ConsenSys Layer Client, TeKu.
共识，我在Teku上工作。
I'm also a maintainer on a couple of REST APIs, which is the beacon API and key manager
我还是几个REST API的维护者，这是Beacon API和密钥经理
API, and they're the main APIs that the ConsenSys Layer uses to do different things.
API，它们是共识层用来做不同事情的主要API。
My team's got seven software engineers in it, and four are in techie, and sorry, four
我的团队中有七位软件工程师，四位在技术人员中，对不起，四个
are in Europe, and three are in the APAC region, but we operate as one team.
在欧洲，三个在亚太地区，但我们是一个团队。
I figured I'd start off with going through at a high level about the consensus layer.
我认为我会从高水平的共识层开始。
Obviously, we've got a number of things that drive what we do on a day-to-day basis.
显然，我们有很多事情可以驱动我们的日常工作。
There's the consensus spec, which is basically the complete executable specification for the consensus layer.
有共识规范，基本上是共识层的完整可执行规范。
There's an execution API, which is our interface to the execution layer client.
有一个执行API，这是我们与执行层客户端的接口。
So that's really important as well.
因此，这也很重要。
In terms of APIs internally, we've got the beacon API, which allows us to do things like produce blocks and submit blocks.
就内部API而言，我们拥有Beacon API，它使我们能够执行诸如生产块并提交块之类的事情。
Then there's the key manager API, which is also important, but it's more around validated key management.
然后是关键管理器API，这也很重要，但更重要的是涉及经过验证的密钥管理。
So being able to accept a new key, being able to remove a key that we're running.
因此，能够接受新密钥，能够删除我们正在运行的密钥。
And then there's the builder API, which is around building the execution layer section
然后是构建器API，它围绕着构建执行层部分
of the block that's in preference to using the execution layer for some people.
优先使用某些人的执行层的块。
Some people fall back to their local execution layer as a default, but some people use the
有些人违约回到本地执行层，但有些人使用
builder API to do MEV.
建造者API要做MEV。
The other thing that does drive teams is obviously their actual team direction.
驱动团队的另一件事显然是他们的实际团队指导。
For Teco as an example, we don't currently implement the light client, so there are sections
以Teco为例，我们目前不实施光线客户端，因此有部分
of the consensus spec that we understand, but we don't necessarily implement.
我们理解的共识规范，但我们不一定实施。
look at everything, basically consensus layer and execution layer, both to find open specifications.
查看所有内容，基本上是共识层和执行层，都可以找到开放的规格。
Prefus Dake itself is basically like a really large, complicated, distributed game.
Prefus Dake本身基本上就像是一个非常大，复杂，分布式的游戏。
Like any games, there's interactions that are pretty well defined, and there's a set of rules.
像任何游戏一样，互动的定义很好，并且有一组规则。
And like any complicated game, there's definitely gray areas where as much as we think that
就像任何复杂的游戏一样，肯定有灰色区域，我们认为
rules are going to be well defined, they're not actually perfectly defined.
规则将得到充分定义，实际上并不是完美定义。
Because the consensus layer uses executable specs it means that we can write tests on
因为共识层使用可执行的规格，所以这意味着我们可以在
those specs and then we can share those tests with all the implementations.
这些规格，然后我们可以与所有实现共享这些测试。
So Tecce, for example, can download all of those tests and run them and just exclude
因此，例如，Tecce可以下载所有这些测试并运行它们，然后排除
the ones that we don't want to cover like the light client.
那些我们不想像光线客户那样涵盖的人。
Looking at Tecce, so our mission statement, if you like, is that we want to be the client
看着tecce，所以我们的使命陈述（如果您愿意的话）是我们想成为客户
of choice for institutional stakers.
适用于机构stakers的选择。
We are written in Java,
我们是用爪哇写的
so hopefully people can read a little bit of Java,
所以希望人们能读一点爪哇，
but it's not going to be super super code heavy today,
但这不会是今天的超级代码，
so it should be good.
所以应该很好。
We've got a lot of extensive metrics
我们有很多广泛的指标
that's exposed through Prometheus,
那是通过普罗米修斯暴露的，
so got a really good dashboard,
所以有一个非常好的仪表板，
which I probably won't show today,
我今天可能不会表现出来，
But we do have it, and it's openly available to everyone
但是我们确实有它，并且公开可供所有人使用
to use.
使用。
And we've got a big focus on testing.
而且我们非常关注测试。
If anyone's seen the testing triangle before,
如果有人以前看过测试三角形，
so you'll have a large number of tests at the unit test level.
因此，您将在单位测试级别进行大量测试。
And then as you go up the triangle,
然后，当您上三角形时，
there's less at the integration level,
在整合级别的少量，
and there's less at the system level.
而且在系统级别上少了。
But covering all levels is generally a good idea
但是覆盖所有级别通常是一个好主意
so that you get the coverage that you need.
这样您就可以获得所需的覆盖范围。
We're pretty focused on logging.
我们非常专注于伐木。
So we use a basic user Log4j.
因此，我们使用基本的用户log4j。
We were impacted by the Log4j thing a couple of years ago, if anyone knows about that.
如果有人知道，几年前，我们受到了Log4J的影响。
I think most client teams were.
我认为大多数客户团队都是。
And we run one code stream.
我们运行一个代码流。
So some client teams will use branch development where they do features in different branches
因此，一些客户团队将使用分支机构开发，在不同的分支机构中进行功能
and then bring them in towards the end.
然后将它们带入最后。
We don't do that.
我们不这样做。
We use development or master development.
我们使用开发或大师开发。
And we release all of our code frequently.
我们经常发布所有代码。
So anything that we do needs to be either active or behind a feature flag.
因此，我们所做的任何事情都需要活跃或在功能标志后面。
If we don't want code to be in the release, we need to make sure that we're disabling
如果我们不希望代码在版本中，我们需要确保我们正在禁用
it.
它。
got a ton of documentation.
有大量文档。
The product is open source, and we do support on Discord
该产品是开源的，我们确实支持不和谐
through the consensus Discord, as well as
通过共识不和谐以及
we do have a presence in the each state Discord,
我们确实在每个状态中都有存在，
and there's a techu support channel there.
那里有一个TechU支持渠道。
And lastly, we are node operators.
最后，我们是节点运算符。
So we run techu on mainnet, and we run techu, obviously,
因此，我们在Mainnet上运行Techu，显然我们运行Techu
on testnets as well.
在测试网上也是如此。
Some people call that eating your own dog food,
有些人称自己吃自己的狗食，
if there's anyone that's heard that before.
如果有人以前听说过。
That was an overview of kind of consensus layer,
那是一种共识层的概述，
and Tecku, are there any questions so far?
和tecku，到目前为止有什么问题吗？
There is only one question,
只有一个问题，
whether Tecku uses Gradle, which I believe it does.
Tecku是否使用Gradle，我相信确实如此。
We do use Gradle, yes. Gradle is our build system, and we currently release to Artifactory.
我们确实使用Gradle，是的。 Gradle是我们的构建系统，我们目前发布到文物中。
And one more now, what is the reason that Teco doesn't implement the Liteclient API?
现在还有一个，TECO不实施持久的API的原因是什么？
Good question. Yeah, for sure.
好问题。是的，肯定。
Basically it's a historical artifact of not having many resources.
基本上，这是没有很多资源的历史文物。
When we started TeKu going towards Phase Zero release, we were down to two developers for
当我们开始teku进入零阶段发布时，我们到了两个开发人员
a while, so it was just no capacity.
一段时间，所以没有能力。
Now that we have seven, we have enough to keep up, but we probably need at least one
现在我们有七个
more resource to be looking at doing a whole new code stream.
更多的资源可以考虑进行全新的代码流。
And we did get some protocol fellowship person
我们确实得到了一些协议奖学金人
to start doing it.
开始这样做。
So there is a start on it,
所以有一个开始，
but we just don't have the resources, basically.
但是我们只是没有资源。
It's not really a focus of the people
这并不是人民的重点
that our business statement are aiming for,
我们的业务声明的目的是
so we haven't found it to be a huge issue.
因此，我们并没有发现这是一个巨大的问题。
but it would be nice to be spec complete as well.
但是，也很高兴能完成规格。
So just competing drivers.
因此，只是竞争驱动程序。
Yeah, get it.
是的，明白了。
Thank you, Paul.
谢谢保罗。
Yeah, I think you can go ahead.
是的，我认为您可以继续前进。
Cool.
凉爽的。
I had a brief look over the material
我简要介绍了材料
that was in the week eight stuff
那是八个东西
and Adrian's talk about all of the modules
和阿德里安（Adrian）谈论所有模块
that were already in techie
已经在技术中
was actually a lot more complete
实际上更加完整
than what I realized.
比我意识到的。
So I haven't gone into the details
所以我还没有详细介绍
of how tech is laid out.
关于技术的布局。
So hopefully people have had a look at that talk,
所以希望人们能看一下那个演讲，
but if they haven't, it's not a huge issue.
但是，如果没有，那不是一个大问题。
We just won't be covering exactly that today
我们只是今天不会涵盖
because there's no point going over the same stuff.
因为毫无意义地讨论相同的事情。
At a very high level,
在很高的水平上
we've laid out our modules in a way
我们以某种方式布置了模块
where it's kind of like a hierarchy.
它有点像层次结构。
So we've got infrastructure at the bottom level.
因此，我们在底层有基础架构。
We've got Ethereum that sits above that.
我们的以太坊高于此。
And basically infrastructure can't pull in anything from Ethereum.
基本上，基础设施无法从以太坊中汲取任何东西。
It can pull in at the same level, but it can't pull in after stack.
它可以在同一级别上拉进去，但是在堆栈后不能吸入。
And that goes the same for the beacon and validator modules,
这对于信标和验证器模块而言相同，
and it goes the same for techie.
技术人员也是如此。
So it can consume all the way down the stack,
因此，它可以一直沿堆栈消耗，
but infrastructure can't consume anywhere up the stack,
但是基础架构无法在堆栈上消耗任何地方，
and B can't consume up the stack.
B无法消耗堆栈。
There are some tools that sit to the side,
有一些工具坐在侧面，
and we do have reference tests.
而且我们确实有参考测试。
But this is kind of our guidance for developers to say,
但这是我们指导开发人员说的指导
make sure that we're not causing cyclic dependencies.
确保我们不会引起循环依赖性。
One of the things that can happen, because IntelliJ is fairly tolerant, we can introduce
可能发生的事情之一，因为Intellij相当宽容，我们可以介绍
a cyclic dependency and not really know, so there are build checks to make sure that we're
循环依赖性且不真正知道，因此有建造检查以确保我们是
consuming things in a nice order and not causing other people problems.
以良好的顺序食用事物，不会导致其他人问题。
Because sometimes when people import the project into Eclipse especially it has caused problems
因为有时候人们将项目导入日食，尤其是引起问题
in the past. Most of the developers use IntelliJ and it doesn't matter a lot, but Eclipse is very
在过去。大多数开发人员都使用Intellij，这并不重要，但是Eclipse非常
opinionated. I'm going to dive first into APIs a little bit, because that's one thing that has
自以为是。我要先深入研究API，因为那是一件事
changed since Adrian gave his talks. They were fairly light on the APIs anyway, but we used to
自阿德里安（Adrian）举行会谈以来发生了变化。无论如何，他们对API都很轻松，但是我们曾经
use an annotated set of objects to do our APIs,
使用带注释的对象进行我们的API，
and now we've changed to a more declarative style.
现在，我们已经更改为更有声明的风格。
If we have a look at where APIs are and what they're used for,
如果我们看一下API的位置以及它们的用途，
in terms of the operator, they may
就操作员而言，他们可能
need to interact with the beacon node,
需要与信标节点互动，
and they may need to interact with Validator Client
他们可能需要与验证器客户端进行互动
for a couple of different reasons.
出于两个不同的原因。
got the beacon API which allows accessing actual data from the beacon
获得了信标API，允许从信标访问实际数据
node. You can get state data, you can get block data, you can
节点。您可以获取状态数据，可以获取块数据，您可以
produce and submit attestations and all of that sort of thing and that will
产生并提交证明以及所有此类事物，这将
go straight on to, like the beacon node will submit it to the network. The
直接进行，就像信标节点将其提交给网络一样。这
Validator client itself is a small client
验证者客户端本身是一个小客户
that is just managing keys and making
那只是管理钥匙并制作
sure that duties are done.
确保完成职责。
And it can use the beacon API to do that.
它可以使用信标API来做到这一点。
But from an operator perspective,
但是从操作员的角度来看
the key manager API allows an operator
密钥管理器API允许操作员
to add or remove a Validator key at runtime.
在运行时添加或删除验证器密钥。
So that's kind of a nifty API.
所以这是一种漂亮的API。
It does require a lot more security.
确实需要更多的安全性。
I think in the Key Manager API, we recommend only using SSL.
我认为在关键经理API中，我们建议仅使用SSL。
And we also recommend it being password protected,
我们还建议它受到密码保护，
because these sorts of things are dealing with private keys,
因为这类事情正在涉及私钥，所以
and it's super, super sensitive.
它是超级敏感的。
So it would be bad if you lost your private keys.
因此，如果您丢失了私钥，那将是不好的。
Hopefully, we all understand that.
希望我们都明白这一点。
I'm happy to go into it, but that's what the KeyManager API
我很高兴参与其中，但这就是Keymanager API
is around.
在附近。
From the Beacon node perspective,
从信标节点的角度来看，
the APIs it mainly consumes are the Engine API
它主要消耗的API是引擎API
to talk to the execution layer, and the Builder API,
与执行层和构建器API交谈，
I believe it's called, to interact with builders
我相信这被称为与建筑商互动
and relays to interact with MEV.
并继电器与MEV互动。
it's not required to be using the builder API.
不需要使用构建器API。
You can simply have a beacon node connected
您只需连接一个信标节点
to an execution layer, which is what I have at home.
执行层，这是我在家中的作品。
It does simplify the setup, and there are situations
它确实简化了设置，并且有情况
where the beacon node might need to turn the builder API off
信标节点可能需要关闭构建器API的位置
so that we can produce blocks, because our number one
这样我们就可以产生块，因为我们的第一
important thing is liveliness of the network.
重要的是网络的生计。
The other API which I won't get into it all today,
我今天将不会全部了解的另一个API，
I won't really touch on anything except the beacon API.
除了Beacon API，我什么都不会涉及。
There's a signer API that allows external signers.
有一个允许外部签名者的签名API。
So if you are using Dirk or Web3 signer,
因此，如果您使用的是Dirk或Web3签名者，
they'll implement the signer API,
他们将实现签名API，
and the Validator client will go via them
验证器客户将通过他们去
to sign rather than signing themselves.
签名而不是签名。
it allows things like sharing a signer and making sure that everything's centrally controlled,
它允许分享签名者并确保所有事物都得到集中控制，
which is a better high-valuability solution than just having a local signer
这是一个更好的高价值解决方案，而不是拥有本地签名者
and having to do flashing protection by yourself.
并且必须自己做闪烁的保护。
So this is probably obvious, but just to state it,
因此，这可能是显而易见的，但只是要陈述它，
API is the interface to the world, and for the world to access the beacon API.
API是世界的界面，也是世界访问Beacon API的界面。
It's secure by default, so for us that means we have an access list, and it's only accessible
默认情况下它是安全的，因此对我们来说，这意味着我们有一个访问列表，并且仅访问
by localhost, and it's accessible only on 127.0.0.1.
由Localhost，仅在127.0.0.1上访问。
We use a declarative interface, which is the interesting bit.
我们使用声明性接口，这是有趣的位。
We ended up having to write our own, which is never my first choice, but in this case
我们最终不得不写自己的书，这永远不是我的第一选择，但是在这种情况下
it made a lot of sense.
这很有意义。
It's called type definitions, and we'll have a look at some examples in a minute.
它称为类型定义，我们将在一分钟内查看一些示例。
And the type definitions allow us to define parts of the object to expose, and parts to
类型定义使我们能够定义对象的一部分以暴露，以及部分
are not explicitly parts to not exposed,
没有明确的零件不暴露，
but basically we can say,
但我们基本上可以说
access these attributes of an object,
访问对象的这些属性，
which is quite useful if we've got an object
如果我们有一个对象，这非常有用
that is slightly different
那略有不同
to what we need to share on the network.
我们需要在网络上分享的内容。
And they're all based on SSZ.
它们都是基于SSZ的。
So SSZ is strongly typed
因此SSZ强烈键入
and it has all of the information
它具有所有信息
about what we want to share.
关于我们要分享的内容。
And we want it to be able to leverage
我们希望它能够利用
the data that's already there
已经存在的数据
so that we don't have to redefine it all on our API layer,
因此，我们不必在API层上重新定义所有这些，
which is what we were doing
这是我们在做的
when we were creating the old objects,
当我们创建旧对象时，
which we'll also run through in a minute.
我们也将在一分钟内完成。
A very simple type def example,
一个非常简单的类型def示例，
we've got a class called post attestation.
我们有一个名为Post Sectestation的课程。
That's when the beacon node
那是信标节点
is actually trying to submit a signed attestation to the beacon node.
实际上是在试图向信标节点提交签名证明。
Sorry, when the Validator client is trying
抱歉，验证器客户端尝试
to submit a signed attestation.
提交签名证明。
This is kind of the structure within the body of the object itself.
这是物体本身体内的结构。
But this is where we're declaring what we want to use.
但这是我们宣布要使用的内容的地方。
So we're saying that in a request body, we have a, I'll stop clicking,
因此，我们说的是，在请求正文中，我们有一个，我会停止点击，
We have a deserializable type definition.
我们有一个可见的类型定义。
So it's going to be coming in across the wire as JSON.
因此，它将像JSON一样跨过电线。
And we're going to consume that JSON
我们要消耗那个JSON
and turn it into a real object.
并将其变成真实的对象。
And we're going to be using the attestation schema.
而且我们将使用证明模式。
So each SSZ object defines its schema,
因此，每个SSZ对象都定义了其模式，
and we're going to be leveraging off the attestation schema.
我们将利用证明模式。
And we're going to be expecting it as JSON.
我们将期待它为JSON。
In terms of responses, OK is a good response.
在回答方面，确定是一个很好的回应。
That's 200 for anyone that loves HTTP codes.
对于喜欢HTTP代码的任何人来说，这是200。
The other code that's likely is a bad request code, which is
其他可能是不良请求代码的代码，即
400.
400。
And a bad request code has to be defined as a JSON type as well.
不良的请求代码也必须定义为JSON类型。
So we tell it, we give it the type of,
所以我们告诉它，我们给它的类型
we give it a declaration of what it's going to look like
我们向它声明它的样子
as a valid object.
作为有效对象。
If we have a look at,
如果我们看，
hopefully that changes, no.
希望这种变化，没有。
Hasn't changed the view anywhere.
在任何地方都没有更改视图。
I was hoping it would stay on the view.
我希望它能保持景色。
Excellent.
出色的。
So, ooh, I'm running out of room.
所以，哦，我耗尽了房间。
That's defined in the constructor.
这是在构造函数中定义的。
And then in the handle request, which is the predefined interface that's there, we basically
然后在句柄请求中，这是存在的预定义接口，我们基本上是
get the request body. And when we call submitAtStations internally, we get a future. So it's an asynchronous
获取请求主体。当我们内部致电提交站时，我们将获得未来。所以这是一种异步
request and we may get a list of data errors. And then basically we respond asynchronously.
请求，我们可能会获取数据错误列表。然后基本上我们异步做出反应。
We need to queue up a response to say, once this future resolves, then we're going to
我们需要排队回答，以说，一旦这个未来解决，我们就会去
go through and render any errors and decide on the error response if there's an actual
如果有实际，请仔细检查任何错误，并决定错误响应
error.
错误。
We have unit tests.
我们有单位测试。
Ooh, I'm going to have to stop and start it a lot.
哦，我将不得不停下来开始它。
Sorry about that.
对此很抱歉。
I should've just clicked on the other link.
我应该只单击另一个链接。
Sorry, I didn't realize it's gonna have to stop and start.
抱歉，我没有意识到它必须停下来开始。
All right, a unit test in JUnit, which is a pretty common framework.
好吧，Junit中的单位测试是一个非常常见的框架。
In the unit test, we're not using mock server or anything complicated.
在单元测试中，我们不使用模拟服务器或任何复杂的东西。
Basically, obviously, we want to make sure that we're able to submit that type of object.
基本上，显然，我们要确保我们能够提交该类型的对象。
So we would submit an attestation type and we would expect it to get back okay, and the
因此，我们会提交认证类型，我们希望它能回来，并且
response body should be null.
响应主体应为无效。
In terms of when there's invalid attestations, we would expect to be able to get errors back
就何时有无效证明而言，我们希望能够恢复错误
and get it and get a bad request response.
并得到它并获得不良的请求响应。
And then we go into some other tests around the body.
然后我们参加了身体周围的其他测试。
I'll have a look at your comment, Josh, in just one second.
我将在短短一秒钟内看一下您的评论，Josh。
That'll be easier.
这会更容易。
Let's try that now.
让我们现在尝试一下。
Share screen.
共享屏幕。
Oh, until our screen.
哦，直到我们的屏幕。
Nice.
好的。
You see it now?
你现在看到了吗？
Cool.
凉爽的。
Yeah.
是的。
Okay.
好的。
That's much better.
那更好。
Did I not click share until our screen?
在我们的屏幕之前，我没有点击共享？
Apparently I don't have permissions to share an entire screen.
显然，我没有共享整个屏幕的权限。
Sorry guys.
对不起。
Are there any questions while I fix this permissions issue?
解决此权限问题时，有什么问题吗？
Yes, there is a one big question about whether you share any libraries with Basu,
是的，关于您是否与Basu共享任何图书馆有一个大问题，
it will be some collaborative work there.
那里将是一些合作的工作。
That's a good question, actually.
实际上，这是一个很好的问题。
We do share a couple of libraries.
我们确实分享了几个图书馆。
The main one is actually around Prometheus.
主要的实际上是在普罗米修斯附近。
So all of our metrics go through a basic library, which
因此，我们所有的指标都通过基本库，该图书馆
is safe just having to implement any of the metrics
安全是否必须实施任何指标
themselves.
自己。
We do have rapid classes that allow us to do our own thing.
我们确实有快速的课程，可以让我们做自己的事情。
I'm just going to have to pretty much re-
我只需要重新
Okay, and we will be back very soon.
好的，我们很快就会回来。
Yeah, Paul is making it so he can share his entire screen.
是的，保罗正在做它，以便他可以分享他的整个屏幕。
I think he didn't realize his browser was running this session.
我认为他没有意识到他的浏览器正在进行这次会议。
So we'll be back right in a moment here.
因此，我们将在这里稍后回来。
Meanwhile, feel free to ask any questions.
同时，请随时提出任何问题。
Also, if you have any questions unanswered from previous consensus-related talks, feel
另外，如果您对以前与共识有关的谈话有任何疑问，请感觉到
free to post them.
免费发布它们。
Hey.
嘿。
Hi, Brian.
嗨，布莱恩。
Can you put me back?
你能把我放回去吗？
Apparently, it couldn't reopen Prime, it means it couldn't reopen this.
显然，它无法重新打开Prime，这意味着它无法重新打开此问题。
Now she'll be able to share the entire screen.
现在，她将能够共享整个屏幕。
I was just saying, we do share base libraries, which is mainly around the metrics.
我只是说，我们确实共享基本库，这主要是围绕指标。
So other than that, I don't think so.
因此，除此之外，我不这么认为。
I know Web3 signup pulls in a lot of our REST API stuff.
我知道Web3注册会吸引许多我们的REST API东西。
I don't think they, hopefully they don't anymore because we're getting rid of most of what
我不认为他们，希望他们不再了，因为我们已经摆脱了大部分
they use.
他们使用。
That is something that I have to chase up on sometime very soon.
这是我很快就必须追赶的事情。
Now I get the fun of logging into everything.
现在，我获得了登录所有内容的乐趣。
Yeah it makes sense, metrics can be basically the same thing but the other parts are very
是的，这很有意义，指标基本上可能是同一回事，但是其他部分非常
different between EL and CL.
EL和CL之间的不同。
And yeah, we'll let you know when there are more questions coming.
是的，当还有更多问题即将到来时，我们会告诉您。
Yep, I'm just logging into, we have a lot of authentication requirements now, so closing
是的，我只是在登录，我们现在有很多身份验证要求，所以关闭
the browser was actually really bad, but I'm getting it.
浏览器实际上真的很糟糕，但是我得到了。
It's always the way.
总是这样。
Let's try again.
让我们再试一次。
No, not slides.
不，不是幻灯片。
That's better.
更好。
Now it's actually changing for you.
现在，它实际上正在为您改变。
One of the things that we noticed was a gap when we were developing APIs actually in the
我们注意到的一件事是当我们在实际上开发API时的差距
when we were using annotations is that we could very easily change the definition of
当我们使用注释时，我们可以很容易地更改
an API and not see that the definition had changed.
API，没有看到定义发生了变化。
it's actually really bad, especially on this API,
实际上真的很糟糕，尤其是在这个API上，
because the definition is really, really important
因为定义确实非常重要
to get right.
做对。
So we ended up basically dumping the JSON schema
所以我们最终基本上倾倒了JSON模式
so that tests can reference that JSON schema
因此测试可以参考JSON模式
to be able to validate that we haven't changed things,
为了验证我们没有改变事物，
or at least show us when we have changed things.
或至少向我们展示我们何时改变了事情。
it's a pretty low tech solution but it's very effective
这是一个非常低的技术解决方案，但非常有效
we end up getting these files where um in this case we're looking at the
我们最终将这些文件获取在这种情况下，我们正在查看
post data stations uh we're looking at the the route eth v1
邮政数据站，我们正在查看路线ETH V1
beacon pool attestations there's two routes on that
信标泳池证明有两条路线
there's a get datagram and there's a post datagram
有一个数据报，有一个帖子数据报
the get's defined here we'll scroll down because we were looking at the post
在这里定义的get定义了，我们会向下滚动，因为我们正在查看帖子
implementation so in terms of the post it has a couple of tags it's it's part of the
实施因此，就帖子而言，它具有几个标签，这是
validator required api which is actually really important to know any validator
验证器所需的API，实际上知道任何验证器真的很重要
that's implementing the rest api has to implement this post function
这是实现REST API必须实现此帖子功能
it's a tag it's a low-tech solution to say you need to implement this but it's
这是一个标签，是一个低技术解决方案，可以说您需要实施此功能
it turned out to be quite effective and then basically we're expecting a rest
事实证明它非常有效，然后我们基本上希望休息
body that has to have the type at a station
车站必须在车站
and the valid responses that we get are 200 400 and 500. 500 got magically added
我们得到的有效响应是200 400和500。500被神奇地添加了
we didn't really want to have to hack in 500 every single interface
我们真的不想在每个界面中进行500个攻击
so we made it part of the default set but we would just already always add
因此，我们使其成为默认集的一部分，但是我们已经始终添加
that um in our declarations this interface was really handy to have when we're switching over
我们声明中的那个界面真的很方便
to type definitions because we were able to then see what we were missing when we were
键入定义，因为我们能够看到我们当时所缺少的
changing the interface rewriting a whole library is a big undertaking and if you don't have
更改界面重写整个库是一项艰巨的任务，如果您没有
adequate testing beforehand you're really not going to have very much fun
事先进行了足够的测试，您真的不会很有趣
um
嗯
Oh man, it's ugly.
哦，丑陋，这很丑陋。
That's most of this example.
这是这个示例的大部分。
Did anyone have any questions on that?
有人对此有任何疑问吗？
The reason that I thought that this might be interesting is because this is our own
我认为这可能很有趣的原因是因为这是我们自己的
So it's not something that you can find online to find references of it's something that you really need to either follow examples or ask one of the techie devs.
因此，您无法在网上找到它可以找到它的参考文献，这是您真正需要遵循示例或询问Techie Devs的内容。
It's interesting. We don't have a question specifically about this example.
很有趣。我们对这个示例没有特别的问题。
But there was another question. Do you use any dependency injection framework?
但是还有另一个问题。您使用任何依赖注入框架吗？
Penance injection framework.
pen悔注射框架。
None comes to mind.
没有人想到。
We do, no, none comes to mind.
我们做，不，没有想到。
We might.
我们可能。
I don't think so.
我不这么认为。
We do have libraries that people use to fuzz and stuff, but that's not really what the
我们确实有人们用来模糊和东西的图书馆，但这并不是真正的
question is. I guess that's injecting fuzzed data, but yeah.
问题是。我想那是注入模糊的数据，但是是的。
Yeah, I say no, but I could be wrong.
是的，我说不，但我可能错了。
Okay, for now. Yeah, thank you, Paul. I think we can we can
好吧，现在。是的，谢谢保罗。我认为我们可以
move along.
继续前进。
The next example is also I love my mouse wheel. Sorry. The next
下一个例子也是我爱我的鼠标轮。对不起。下一个
The other example I'm going to go into is also around using the type definitions.
我要输入的另一个示例也是使用类型定义。
This one's slightly different because what we end up doing is we bring in an object which
这个略有不同，因为我们最终要做的是我们带来一个对象
isn't our own wrapper object called objectInMetadata.
不是我们自己的包装对象称为ObjectinMetadata。
We were finding that often we need to return some sort of generic object.
我们发现通常需要返回某种通用对象。
And in this case, it's a bytes 32.
在这种情况下，它是一个字节32。
In some cases, it's an entire block.
在某些情况下，这是整个块。
But with that data, we also need whether it's finalized and whether it's in post merge world,
但是有了这些数据，我们还需要它是否最终确定以及是否在合并后的世界中，
there's a mode called execution optimistic.
有一种称为执行乐观的模式。
So we don't really have all of the data.
因此，我们并没有真正拥有所有数据。
we think that it's valid but we don't really have the data from the EL.
我们认为这是有效的，但我们实际上没有EL的数据。
So we found that we needed that type of definition a lot and we created this container for it.
因此，我们发现我们非常需要这种类型的定义，并为其创建了此容器。
So we can pass it in an object and metadata that contains bytes 32.
因此，我们可以将其传递到包含字节32的对象和元数据中。
And in this case, although we have that structure, we need a different structure
在这种情况下，尽管我们有这种结构，但我们需要一个不同的结构
to output and that's why this is more interesting in a way than the last one.
输出，这就是为什么这比最后一个更有趣的原因。
We've got, we're defining a field that is data and to get that data field it's actually
我们已经有了，我们正在定义一个是数据的字段，并且要获取该数据字段实际上是
of root type so it's actually recursing into this definition which has a field which is
根类型，因此它实际上是在这个定义中递归的，该定义具有一个字段
root and it's bytes 32.
根，是字节32。
So that's the actual data payload of this get block root function.
因此，这就是此GET块根功能的实际数据有效载荷。
It's also got the execution optimistic flag, which
它也有执行的乐观标志，
just comes straight off the object,
只是直接从物体上
and the finalized flag, which just
和最终标志，仅
comes straight off the object.
直接从物体上脱离。
This one, the testing is actually very similar.
这是一个非常相似的测试。
So it should return header block information.
因此，它应该返回标头块信息。
We try and use mostly meaningful test names.
我们尝试使用主要有意义的测试名称。
Sometimes they get exceedingly long,
有时它们很长，
but we do try and make them fairly descriptive.
但是我们确实尝试使它们相当描述。
And it's a source of code-reviewed comments
它是经过代码评论的评论的来源
all the time.
一直以来。
The metadata ones, again, are very similar to the other test.
同样，元数据与其他测试非常相似。
What we're doing here is validating
我们在这里做的是验证
that that type definition has everything that we need.
该类型的定义具有我们需要的一切。
So we know that we need to be able to return a 200 response,
因此，我们知道我们需要能够返回200个响应，
and we know that we need to be able to turn it 400 response.
而且我们知道我们需要能够将其转换为400。
If the object definition doesn't contain those,
如果对象定义不包含这些，
then we're in trouble, because it'll turn a 400 response
然后我们遇到了麻烦，因为它会变成400个响应
into a 500 response, and a 500 is an internal error, which
进行500响应，而500是内部错误，这是
is still an error, but it's not a great response from a REST
仍然是一个错误，但这不是休息的很好的回应
API.
API。
But basically the unit tests are more interested in that metadata definition
但是基本上，单位测试对该元数据定义更感兴趣
And the integration tests are more interested in actually what happens when you get
并且集成测试实际上对您获得的实际情况更感兴趣
In this case, the object definition itself, I guess
在这种情况下，我猜对象定义本身
This one's fairly easy because it's mostly a block root
这很容易，因为它主要是块根
So it's throwing out to another object, which we won't look at.
因此，它将其扔到另一个对象，我们不会看。
Get block root isn't heavily used.
获得块根并不大量使用。
The other one, the post attestation, is heavily used.
另一个是后证明，大量使用了。
So the other one gets tested every time we run up a validator
因此，每次我们运行验证器时，另一个都会进行测试
that's in remote mode.
那是偏远模式。
It'll be using that interface, and we'll know very quickly if it breaks.
它将使用该界面，我们很快就会知道它是否破裂。
The other thing we do have when we're looking at APIs is this is our own version of the documentation,
当我们查看API时，我们还有另一件事是这是我们自己的文档版本，
but this is also on the Deacon APIs repository.
但这也位于执事APIS存储库上。
There's a way to look at the object definitions.
有一种方法可以查看对象定义。
So this is the interface that we were looking at just then.
因此，这是我们在那时所寻找的界面。
It has a path parameter, which is the block ID.
它具有路径参数，即块ID。
The funny thing, I think, with this one is that you can pass things like head, or you can pass the block root, which I think that's just because block ID is a standard definition, but it seems a little bit weird to be able to pass the block root and then get the block root back.
我认为，有趣的是，您可以通过诸如头部之类的东西，或者可以通过块根，我认为这仅仅是因为块ID是标准的定义，但是能够有点奇怪通过块根，然后将块根返回。
But that's just one of those weird design outcomes that can happen sometimes.
但这只是有时可能发生的怪异设计成果之一。
So that is a relatively simple example, a couple of examples on type definitions.
因此，这是一个相对简单的示例，即类型定义的几个示例。
I'm going to move on from APIs in a second. Is there any other questions on APIs before we
我将在一秒钟内从API继续前进。在我们之前，还有其他关于API的问题吗
I don't see anything specific about APIs at the moment.
目前，我没有看到有关API的具体内容。
Yeah.
是的。
Cool.
凉爽的。
We'll get cracking into the next section.
我们将进入下一节。
I gather you've looked a bit at ERPs and the EIP process.
我聚集在一起，您已经看了ERP和EIP过程。
I'm not across the entire process, so this is all from the perspective of a developer
我不在整个过程中，所以从开发人员的角度来看这一切
who's starting on the prototyping section.
谁从原型制作部分开始。
So I may be misrepresenting things, but here's kind of my take on it.
因此，我可能会歪曲事情，但这是我对此的看法。
So we get to a point in time in the EIP process where we're not just a research project anymore,
因此，我们在EIP过程中达到了一个时间点，我们不再只是一个研究项目，
and we want to start looking at how we're going to implement something.
我们想开始研究如何实施某些东西。
So we start in this round of kind of prototyping,
因此，我们从这一轮原型制作开始
and it's no longer research. We often discuss these things on Discord,
这不再是研究。我们经常在不和谐上讨论这些事情，
so ETH, R&D, Discord. For some things that are larger
因此，ETH，研发，不和谐。对于某些更大的东西
there's dedicated channels, sometimes they are on Telegram, it
有专门的频道，有时它们在电报上，
it just depends where the conversation starts.
这仅取决于对话的开始。
And often it ends up being a bridge between the two.
通常，它最终是两者之间的桥梁。
It's a fairly organic and muddy process.
这是一个相当有机和泥泞的过程。
So it is hard to understand what happens
因此很难理解会发生什么
because it's not always the same.
因为它并不总是一样。
When we're doing this, we're looking at things from more
当我们这样做时，我们正在查看更多
of an engineering mindset.
工程心态。
So we're looking at more holistically
所以我们更整体地看待
the system that's there now and trying to fit something into that system with knowledge
现在已经存在的系统，并试图用知识将某些东西安装到该系统中
of the rest of it.
其余的。
So it's kind of this case of we're trying to make the EIP actually fit into an executable
因此，这种情况是我们试图使EIP真正适合可执行
spec and make sure that we understand how the EL and CL are going to interact.
规格并确保我们了解EL和CL如何相互作用。
And sometimes there's definitely missed bits.
有时肯定会错过。
After an ERP's been mostly accepted and working out
在ERP被大多接受并锻炼之后
the details is a big part of how things go.
细节是事情的发展很大。
This is all very vague and hand-wavy,
这都是非常模糊和手动的，
and we'll move into a concrete example where I can explain
我们将进入一个具体的例子，我可以解释
more what I'm talking about.
更多我在说什么。
ERP 7251 is around maximum effective balance
ERP 7251在最大的有效余额附近
being increased.
增加。
and it is true that i'm looking at this because i'm currently implementing it
的确，我正在考虑这个，因为我目前正在实施它
and i feel like i have a reasonable understanding so basically as part of
而且我觉得我基本上有一个合理的理解
this we're looking at the initial penalty when a slashing event occurs
当发生削减事件时，我们正在查看最初的处罚
um the slashing event uh gets expensive even for a single validator we're looking at
嗯，削减的事件uh uh也变得昂贵，即使我们正在寻找一个验证者
it, 1E, being the initial penalty that one of the current validators would incur if they
它是1E，是当前验证者之一如果他们将蒙受的最初罚款
were to be slashed.
被砍了。
And just to be clear, because slashing is used a lot in a lot of different ways, anytime
只是要清楚，因为随时用多种不同的方式使用了削减
someone incurs a penalty on the network, we just call that a penalty.
有人在网络上受到罚款，我们只是将其称为罚款。
if someone has done something intentionally bad
如果有人做了故意不好的事情
and we deem it bad enough
我们认为它足够糟糕
that they should stop participating on the network,
他们应该停止参与网络，
we call that a slashing and only that a slashing.
我们将其称为削减，只是削减了这一点。
So the result of what I'm calling being slashed
所以我所说的被削减的结果
is literally being kicked off the network.
实际上是被启动了网络。
The initial penalty for a small validator isn't too bad,
小验证器的最初处罚还不错，
but once we scale it up to max EB,
但是，一旦我们将其扩展到Max EB，
the initial penalty with the rest of the rule set today would look like 64 ETH.
当今其余规则的最初罚款看起来像64 ETH。
It's linear scaling so in some worlds you could argue that that's fair
这是线性的缩放，所以在某些世界中，您可以说这是公平的
but the reality is if I was to have 64 validators on a box
但是现实是，如果我要在一个盒子上有64个验证器
and one of them gets an attestation slashing
其中一个被证明削减了
the rest could be perfectly fine for a period of time
剩下的一段时间都很好
depending on which slot they're attesting to.
取决于他们证明哪个插槽。
So I could turn that node off and I would have only been slashed for one validator or a small number of validators.
因此，我可以关闭该节点，只为一个验证器或少量验证器而被削减。
In the case of consolidating all of that into a single validator, I would have incurred 100% of the penalty when previously I would have only incurred a small percentage.
如果将所有这些合并到一个验证器中，那么我将只会产生少量的罚款时，我会产生100％的罚款。
So from that perspective, it's not super fair.
因此，从这个角度来看，这并不公平。
So what they're looking to do is for the initial penalty, make sure that that initial penalty approaches nothing, which works for everyone.
因此，他们想要做的是最初的罚款，请确保最初的罚款对每个人都无效。
It's not penalizing institutionals.
这不是对机构的惩罚。
It's not penalizing solo stakers.
这不是惩罚独奏的人。
is.
是。
When we had a look at this to put into the spec,
当我们看一下将其放入规格中时，
the thought came to mind around whistleblower rewards.
举报人奖励的想法想到了。
What happens when you get slashed
当您被砍伐时会发生什么
is that someone gets a reward for reporting it.
是有人向报告获得奖励​​。
In reality, it's the block proposer.
实际上，这是块提议者。
In theory, it could have been a third party that produces,
从理论上讲，它可能是产生的第三方
that's going over all of the data
这是所有数据
and trying to report on who's been banned.
并试图报告被禁止的人。
In this case, our 2048 ETH Validator, which is the max,
在这种情况下，我们的2048 ETH验证器（最大）
would have created a 4 ETH whistleblower award, which
本来会创建4个ETH举报人奖，
is awesome, and a lot of people would be really happy.
很棒，很多人会很高兴。
But the problem with that is we're actually minting ETH.
但是问题是我们实际上是在铸造ETH。
The penalty no longer pays for that whistleblower award, which
罚款不再支付该举报人奖，这是
If we go back to game theory it's infinite resource generation and it's something to be avoided.
如果我们回到游戏理论，它是无限的资源产生，这是避免的。
So ultimately, we don't want to mint ETH.
因此，最终，我们不想造成Eth。
The solution for this is the whistleblower reward needs to at least be covered by the initial penalty.
这样做的解决方案是至少必须涵盖举报人的奖励。
That's an interesting case of when an EIP gets to the real world.
这是一个有趣的案例，即EIP何时进入现实世界。
I'm just going to read a question.
我只是要读一个问题。
We have one question here regarding the changes here.
我们在这里有一个问题有关此处的更改。
Is it looking at Phase 0 spec?
它正在查看阶段0规格吗？
That sounds like about Phase 0 spec.
这听起来像是阶段0规格。
I'll have to get back to you on that one,
我必须在那个方面找你
but I'm fairly sure.
但是我很确定。
it changed in Bellatrix to be 1e, I'm fairly sure.
我很确定，它在Bellatrix中变为1E。
If anyone's been looking at the consensus spec,
如果有人在研究共识规范，
the other thing we do is we create basically a difference
我们要做的另一件事是我们基本上创造了一个差异
between the previous version and the next version
在上一个版本和下一个版本之间
as a definition of the next version.
作为下一个版本的定义。
So it can be confusing to follow,
因此，它可能会令人困惑，
But I can chase up that question, Marius.
但是我可以追逐这个问题，马里乌斯。
I can't answer it right now.
我现在无法回答。
But I'm fairly sure in Bellatrix it changed to be 1E.
但是我很确定，在贝拉特里克斯（Bellatrix）中，它变为1e。
Basically, the reward question changed.
基本上，奖励问题发生了变化。
Yeah, I copied the question for Paul, so it's a bit long.
是的，我为Paul复制了这个问题，所以有点长了。
But we have this discussion in Discord,
但是我们在不和谐中进行了讨论
so maybe if you will join our Discord
因此，也许如果您会加入我们的不和谐
Yeah, okay. Do you want to just shoot me a DM link for that?
是的，好吧。您想为此射击我一个DM链接吗？
Yeah, I will. Awesome. Otherwise I'll forget for sure.
是的，我会的。惊人的。否则我会肯定的是。
Anyway, when we pointed out that the initial penalty would go to 64, no one else in that
无论如何，当我们指出最初的罚款将被罚款64时，没有其他人
in that group argued, so it's probably that I was right, but I can confirm that.
在那个小组中，我可能是对的，但我可以确认这一点。
Um,
嗯，
So basically all of the features, all of the ERP's when they go into the consensus spec
因此，基本上所有功能，所有ERP都进入共识规范时的功能
go into this underscore features folder.
进入此下划线功能文件夹。
And in this case, we've changed Validere now as well.
在这种情况下，我们现在也更改了有效。
We had only changed beacon chain and fork, but it looks like we've now changed another
我们只更换了信标链和叉子，但是看来我们现在改变了另一个
file.
文件。
These are a difference on the specification, so when they say, we're going to be jumping
这些是规格上的不同，所以当他们说，我们将跳跃
into one specifically, I think, we're going to be going to the beacon state.
我认为，具体来说，我们将去标准州。
All right, it's not so with the beacon state.
好吧，信标国家并非如此。
So these redefine the object, and then at a point we start getting new in, say, we know
因此，这些重新定义了对象，然后在某个时候我们开始恢复新手，我们知道
7, 2, 5, 1 is what we're looking at.
我们正在寻找7、2、5、1。
We've actually added a whole ton of new fields
实际上，我们添加了大量新领域
into the Bitcoin state for 7, 2, 5, 1.
进入比特币状态7、2、5、1。
So that's all of these.
这就是所有这些。
Some of them are lists, which are
其中一些是列表，
going to prove interesting.
要证明很有趣。
Someone the other day noticed that this
前几天有人注意到这个
is kind of the first time that we're
是我们第一次
going to be having the splice lists.
将有剪接列表。
That's going to be a pain point that we
这将是我们的痛苦点
haven't worked through yet.
尚未完成。
But in real terms, generally, when we're adding things to the state,
但实际上，通常，当我们向国家添加东西时，
we're adding one or two fields, not eight.
我们添加一个或两个字段，而不是八个字段。
So, yeah, it's going to get interesting.
所以，是的，这会变得有趣。
What I was going to show is...
我要展示的是...
I might actually jump over to my idea.
我实际上可能会跳到我的想法。
it becomes a bit interesting when we add things to our
当我们将东西添加到我们的
uh our code base because of the history of how things have kind of evolved so
嗯，我们的代码基础是因为事物如何发展的历史
we do have changes in our in our um in our actual versioned area
我们在实际版本领域的UM中确实有变化
but we have this whole set of changes in our API area, API schema.
但是我们在API区域API模式中进行了整个变化。
These are the old annotated objects that we used to use.
这些是我们过去使用的旧注释对象。
No, that's not what I clicked on.
不，那不是我点击的内容。
This is?
这是？
No, that's JSON.
不，那是Json。
And balance deposit.
和余额存款。
Okay, that looks better.
好的，看起来更好。
So with our annotated objects, we have to, they're called POJOs, the plain old Java objects,
因此，有了我们的带注释的对象，我们必须将它们称为pojos，普通的旧爪哇对象，
but basically we have to put annotations on every field that we add, and we have to put
但是基本上，我们必须在添加的每个字段上注释，我们必须放置
annotations into the constructor.
注释构造函数。
We also need to create a constructor that allows us to take the real object, the versioned
我们还需要创建一个构造函数，使我们可以采用真实对象，版本
object and produce this object so that we can convert both ways so we need to be able to go
对象并产生此对象，以便我们可以转换这两种方式，以便我们需要能够去
to the schema objects and from the schema objects depending on on the scenario this is basically
到架构对象和架构对象，取决于场景上的对象，这基本上是
this whole folder basically is tech debt because we don't use it anymore except for in some specific
整个文件夹基本上是技术债务，因为我们不再使用它
scenarios but it still needs to be defined because it's changing the state and the old
方案，但仍然需要定义，因为它正在改变状态和旧状态
API still references this. We use these for some of the Validator API, sorry for some of the
API仍然引用此。我们将它们用于某些验证器API，对某​​些
Validator clients interactions with the beacon node but it doesn't it doesn't require state but
验证者客户端与信标节点的交互，但不需要状态，而是
but we haven't removed that code path completely,
但是我们还没有完全删除该代码路径，
so we still are maintaining those objects,
因此，我们仍然维护这些对象，
which is a bit unfortunate.
有点不幸。
Having said that, it's a small change
话虽如此，这是一个很小的变化
compared to the rest of the stuff,
与其他东西相比
which all has to exist anyway.
无论如何都必须存在。
If we have a look just at the JSON object,
如果我们只是看json对象，
all a few new fields will be in there.
所有新领域都将在那里。
they're also defined down through here so that's kind of what it looks like in JSON land and that's
它们也在这里定义了，所以这在Json Land中的外观
where these tests are fairly handy is because changing the object has then changed the type
这些测试相当方便的地方是因为更改对象然后更改了类型
definition that the object uses and that flows through the object at the all of the
对象使用并流过所有物体的定义
integration testing so we can see exactly what's changed without looking at the code
集成测试，因此我们可以在不查看代码的情况下确切地看到发生了什么变化
and same thing if one of these had changed from in un64 to something else
如果其中之一从UN64中变成了其他事物，则同样的事情
that would also be reflected here and we'd be able to see that very easily
这也会在这里反映，我们可以很容易地看到
it's a whole bit of a we have builders and at the moment this is only on my own branch so I've kind
这是我们拥有建筑商的一整体，目前这只是我自己的分支
hacked in some constants which I won't be doing by the time it reaches real code
在某些常数中被黑客入侵，我不会在达到真实代码时做到这一点
but it was an easy way to get this off the ground.
但这是一种使它脱离地面的简单方法。
I'm assuming everyone's seen the builder pattern before so I won't jump much into the builder
我假设每个人都看过建筑商的模式，所以我不会跳入建造者
pattern. The main thing I was going to say is there's a whole lot of stuff that changes just
图案。我要说的主要内容是有很多东西只是改变
for those eight fields so it ends up in a big overhead for the team to wear
对于那八个领域
and that integration test was the annoying test that shows what we've missed basically
该集成测试是令人讨厌的测试，它基本上显示了我们错过了什么
this is one of the few times that we've used branch development
这是我们使用分支开发的几次
normally what we'll do is we'll just put things behind feature toggles
通常，我们会做的是我们只是将事情放在功能切换后面
uh at the moment we've got a case where we've got some some features have been accepted into
嗯，目前我们已经接受了一些功能已被接受
Electra and some are still being worked out and and 7251 is one of those has been worked out so
伊莱克特拉和有些仍在制定中，而7251是已经解决的一项，所以
it's been it hasn't been fully accepted and it hasn't been changed to yes it's definitely in
一直还没有被完全接受，而且还没有更改为是的，它肯定是在
Electra. So I'm keeping it on a branch so that I don't infect the other things, because once I add
伊莱克因此，我将其保留在分支上，以免感染其他东西，因为一旦我添加
those objects into the state, then any other client that we talk to would need to be also
这些对象进入状态，然后我们与之交谈的任何其他客户都需要成为
dealing with the same state, otherwise it's going to get a different route,
处理同一状态，否则将获得不同的路线，
and we won't be able to talk to each other.
而且我们将无法互相交谈。
um another example from 7251 a really seemingly simple one is um is eligible for activation queue
嗯，来自7251的另一个示例一个看似简单的一个um是符合激活队列的条件
so this is a function that is that is having a look at a validator object and determining
因此，这是一个可以查看验证器对象并确定的函数
whether it needs is is able to go into the activation queue to be to become an active
它是否需要进入激活队列以成为活跃
file editor.
文件编辑器。
In Python, everything is snake case.
在Python中，一切都是蛇案。
In Java, it's really confusing to have
在Java，拥有
mixed case where some things are snake case
混合有些事情是蛇案的混合案例
and some things are camel case.
有些事情是骆驼盒。
And all the main Java coding standards are camel case.
所有主要的Java编码标准都是骆驼壳。
So we've gone with camel case.
所以我们已经使用了骆驼盒。
And if we translate that, we get is eligible for activation queue
如果我们翻译了这一点，我们将符合激活队列的资格
much more like that.
更像是这样。
One of these should be found when we do
当我们这样做时，应该找到其中之一
a search through the code.
通过代码进行搜索。
So we'll have a look at the code in a second.
因此，我们将在一秒钟内查看代码。
It was in abstract epoch processor, which is good.
它是在抽象的时期处理器中，这很好。
And then we can have a look at how we're going to define
然后我们可以看一下如何定义
is it eligible for activation queue for Electra,
它是否有资格获得electra的激活队列
which has to change that function.
必须更改该功能。
So if I jump back into it's a lot smaller change.
因此，如果我跳回去，则更改要小得多。
The abstract, you put processR.
摘要，您将processr放置。
The interesting thing is that it was inline, which is OK.
有趣的是，它是内联的，没关系。
And we had a comment which was mentioning it is eligible for activation queue.
我们有一个评论，提到它有资格参加激活队列。
If we have a look back at the spec, it's basically doing the same thing.
如果我们回顾规格，它基本上是在做同样的事情。
It's just a little bit different.
有点不同。
But it sounds like we're just trying to make sure that we don't have to read the whole validator object so that we can make this determination.
但这听起来好像我们只是在试图确保我们不必阅读整个验证器对象，以便我们可以做出确定。
So without changing that logic, I've just split it out into a function.
因此，在不更改该逻辑的情况下，我只是将其分为一个函数。
and basically then I just can override that function when we're looking in.
基本上，当我们看时，我只能覆盖该功能。
I've gone to the wrong file.
我去了错误的文件。
So abstractEqualProcessor.
如此摘要等级。
And so is eligible for activation queue is now dependent on min activation balance,
因此，符合激活队列的条件现在取决于最小激活平衡，
which is a new field that's coming into play in 7.2.5.1.
这是一个在7.2.5.1中发挥作用的新领域。
Along with that, there was a bunch of other functions that needed to be defined.
随之而来的是，还有许多其他功能需要定义。
As compounding withdrawal credential is compounding withdrawal credential.
由于复利的提款证书正在加剧撤回凭证。
I don't know that it makes it that much easier to pass through just the withdrawal credentials.
我不知道这使得通过撤回凭证变得容易得多。
I'm assuming that was done for tests.
我假设这是为了测试。
it's an overhead that I don't care greatly for but it's not either like a big problem so I've
这是我不太在意的开销，但这并不是一个大问题，所以我
just done it the way the spec does it initially and then there's a get max effect validate a max
刚刚按照规格进行操作的方式，然后有一个get max效应验证max
effective balance which does make sense because we have to check the withdrawal credential prefix
有意义的有效平衡，因为我们必须检查提款凭证前缀
if anyone's had a look at
如果有人看着
the dirty details of
肮脏的细节
the validator.
验证器。
We've got a prefix which is 0x00.
我们有一个前缀为0x00。
When withdrawals were active in Capella,
当戒断活动在Capella时，
actually well before that,
实际上，在此之前，
there became this eth1 withdrawal
这是ETH1撤离
which is basically 0x01
基本上是0x01
and then a whole bunch of zeros
然后一堆零
and then an eth address.
然后是ETH地址。
we're going to be leveraging on that and making it 0x02 for compounding.
我们将利用这一点，并将其制作为0x02进行复合。
I wouldn't suggest anyone watching this changes their users 0x02 at the moment.
目前，我不建议任何人观看此事更改他们的用户0x02。
There's nothing stopping you, but it's probably not good
没有什么阻止你的，但这可能不是很好
until we determine all the details to change to.
直到我们确定要更改为的所有细节。
Anyway, the 0x01 is the most common that you'll see on the mainnet now,
无论如何，0x01是您现在在主网上看到的最常见的
which means that withdrawals are basically worked through in a loop
这意味着取款基本上是在循环中进行的
and over a period of a few days,
在几天的时间里，
everyone gets their partial withdrawals processed.
每个人都处理了部分提款。
The new compounding one will change that a little bit
新的复合将会改变一点
and the details aren't finalized yet
细节尚未确定
as to exactly what that's going to look like.
至于那将是什么样子。
We have a bunch of presets that get changed to add some new fields.
我们有一堆预设可以更改以添加一些新字段。
And we have different network configs.
我们有不同的网络配置。
So mainnet, obviously, is the one that most people are aware of.
因此，显然，主网是大多数人所知道的。
Minimal is a handy network config for running during development, because it doesn't need
最小值是一个方便的网络配置，可以在开发过程中运行，因为它不需要
quite so many things, but it does start from phase zero.
很多事情，但它确实从零阶段开始。
And Swift is one that we really only use for testing.
Swift是我们实际上仅用于测试的一种。
It's very, very short epoch time,
这是非常非常短的时期时间，
so it allows us to do things like run acceptance tests
因此，它使我们能够进行诸如运行接受测试之类的事情
in a very fast way where we get to finalization
以一种非常快速的方式进行最终确定
without having to wait for several minutes.
不必等待几分钟。
But they all need to be updated for Electra.
但是它们都需要更新Electra。
So that's just going through that.
所以这就是经历。
and then we have these objects in testing that basically just define some defaults
然后，我们在测试中有这些对象，这些对象基本上只是定义了一些默认值
they're fairly arbitrary so I haven't defined perfectly each value but they give us a
它们是相当任意的，所以我还没有完美地定义每个值，但它们给了我们一个
representative for writing test seconds
代表写作测试秒
So that change is a lot smaller, but it is also only targeting one function, and we've
因此，更改要小得多，但它也只针对一个功能，我们已经
ended up implementing three or four, because we're looking at that min activation balance.
最终实施了三到四个，因为我们正在研究该最小激活平衡。
So that's kind of what you go through when you're prototyping out the functions.
因此，当您原型阐明功能时，这就是您经历的事情。
Obviously, there's tests involved, and there's a framework that we will have to add to.
显然，涉及测试，我们必须添加一个框架。
So when reference tests are added to the spec, we'll be able to then call some of these individual
因此，当将参考测试添加到规格中时，我们将能够致电其中一些人
functions to validate that they're doing what we think they're doing.
功能以验证他们正在做我们认为正在做的事情。
But for now, we don't have those, so we're just implementing the code itself.
但是目前，我们还没有这些，所以我们只是在实施代码本身。
That was a little bit random.
那是随机的。
Is there any questions on that?
有什么问题吗？
Not questions on this part,
对此没有问题，
maybe something for later,
也许以后
but some un-dragged question.
但是一些未拖累的问题。
What is the database that,
什么是数据库，
what is the database engine that Teco uses?
TECO使用的数据库引擎是什么？
Apparently we got two.
显然我们有两个。
When we started at Genesis, we were using RocksDB only.
当我们从创世纪开始时，我们仅使用rockSDB。
We had problems with being able to upgrade RocksDB sometimes,
有时我们能够升级RocksDB时遇到问题，
and they do have a lot of kind of false starts
他们确实有很多错误的开始
with some of their releases where all of a sudden things regress.
随着他们的一些释放，突然的事情会回归。
So we did switch to LevelDB.
因此，我们确实切换到LevelDB。
We have found that LevelDB is not really very actively maintained now.
我们发现LevelDB现在并不是真正积极地维护的。
So we are considering switching back to RocksDB.
因此，我们正在考虑切换回RockSDB。
Basu obviously uses RocksDB,
巴苏显然使用rocksdb，
and there's a lot of expertise in that area in the greater team.
大团队中的那个领域有很多专业知识。
And for anyone that is curious,
对于任何好奇的人
ConsenSys does run a large team of people
共识确实经营着一大批人
maintaining Hyperledger Basu as well.
也维持超级巴苏。
So that's why Basu is sometimes a consideration for Tecku
这就是为什么巴苏有时是对泰克的考虑
in how we're doing our development
在我们的发展方面
because we do have a lot of expertise
因为我们确实有很多专业知识
inside our own group
在我们自己的小组内
for a lot of basic stuff as well.
对于很多基本的东西。
All right, thank you.
好的，谢谢。
That's interesting, yeah,
很有趣，是的，
because it was a get moved from level DB to pedal
因为这是从级别的DB转移到踏板
and it's interesting to hear that you go back to level DB.
有趣的是，您可以回到DB级。
Thank you.
谢谢。
And another question,
还有另一个问题
What do you find most challenging in the tech development,
您在技术开发中发现最具挑战性的是什么，
which part of the code base are the hardest to maintain
代码库的哪一部分最难维护
to work on the quality features?
从事质量功能？
Storage is the hardest for sure.
存储肯定是最难的。
The database storage doesn't change very often.
数据库存储的变化很少。
So what you get with that is basically the tests
因此，您得到的基本上是测试
aren't heavily understood sometimes,
有时对
They're written by usually people that have left the team
他们通常是由离开团队的人写的
because it's not super common that we need to change them.
因为我们需要更改它们并不普遍。
So once we do eventually dive into changing anything
因此，一旦我们最终潜入改变任何东西
in the storage layer, it tends to be a little bit of an overhead.
在存储层中，它往往有点开销。
There's a gentleman in Europe that's been here
欧洲有一位绅士在这里
a little bit less than me, but for a fair while.
比我少一点，但是有一段时间。
So usually it falls back to one of us
所以通常它落在我们一个人身上
to be having an eye over any storage change.
要关注任何存储更改。
And there are sections of the code.
并且有代码的各个部分。
So when we look at the two ways we can run,
因此，当我们查看我们可以运行的两种方式时，
we can run as a beacon node that's combined
我们可以作为组合的信标节点运行
to be able to run Val editor keys in the same process.
能够在相同的过程中运行Val编辑器键。
Or we can run with a split out Val editor client.
或者我们可以使用分解的Val编辑器客户端运行。
So those, in those two modes, there's a parent class for each one.
因此，在这两种模式中，每个人都有一个父母班级。
There's a beacon chain controller, and there's a validated client service, I believe it is
有一个信标连锁控制器，并且有一个经过验证的客户服务，我相信这是
off the top of my head.
从我的头顶上。
Those two are like the parent classes where everything is built from.
这两个就像父母所建造的父母。
But if you need to add something like the key manager API, which could be run in that
但是，如果您需要添加诸如密钥管理器API之类的内容，则可以在其中运行
combined process, or it could be run in the validated client service, you really need
合并过程，也可以在经过验证的客户服务中运行，您确实需要
to be understanding where your flag's going to become active.
了解您的国旗将在哪里活跃。
We use pico-cli for our command-like flag argument
我们使用pico-cli进行类似命令的标志参数
processing stuff.
处理内容。
Right.
正确的。
Interesting.
有趣的。
And so you have two distinct classes for the beacon node
因此，您有两个截然不同的标准节点
and the validator.
和验证器。
We had a question about the validator code,
我们对验证器代码有一个疑问，
but I think we can get into that later,
但是我认为我们稍后可以进入
and you can just keep going and finish the presentation
您可以继续前进并完成演示文稿
this we have yeah over an hour now so uh yeah for sure we'll just keep it going
我们现在有一个多小时，所以呃，肯定会继续下去
i have i have a couple of other slides but um
我还有其他几张幻灯片，但是
they were really in case i ran out of time but this is this kind of wraps up the uh the eip
他们真的是，以防万一我没时间，但这就是这样包裹的
kind of thing that we're looking at so in terms of
我们正在研究的一种事情
of how our team is operating, we'll allocate an owner
我们的团队的运作方式，我们将分配一个所有者
to an individual EIP.
到个人EIP。
So some people, for example, would have got EIP7002,
因此，例如，有些人会有EIP7002，
which is an Electra-confirmed EIP, and it's quite small.
这是一个由Electra确认的EIP，而且很小。
And some people, like me, got the Maxi-B EIP,
有些人，像我一样，都获得了超长
which is quite a lot larger.
大得多。
The person who owns it is going to obviously
拥有它的人显然会
break that project down into tickets or, I've said chunks
将该项目分成门票，或者我说的是
here, but basically issues on GitHub.
在这里，但基本上是在Github上发出的。
Ideally, we're going to present an overview to the team
理想情况下，我们将向团队介绍
so that people understand what's involved in the changes
使人们了解变化涉及的内容
and have a bit of an overview of everything.
并对所有内容有一点概述。
And then that person's going to be
然后那个人将成为
kind of on the hook for making sure
有点在钩子上确保
that things are delivered.
这些东西是交付的。
So just making sure that test nets are all,
因此，只要确保测试网就是
we're joining them, we're not having any issues on them,
我们正在加入他们，我们没有任何问题，
if the spec changes, keeping up with those developments.
如果规格改变了，请跟上这些发展。
And depending on the feature itself,
并取决于功能本身，
7.0.0.2 was quite small
7.0.0.2很小
and it was easily implemented by one person,
它很容易由一个人实施，
but Max-EB is looking like
但是Max-eb看起来像
it's going to be quite a large feature.
这将是一个很大的功能。
Blobs, for example, was a very large feature,
例如，斑点是一个非常大的功能，
and we had half of our team on Blobs.
而且我们有一半的团队在斑点上。
So you might not be implementing the entire feature
因此，您可能不会实现整个功能
depending on that size.
取决于这个大小。
Withdrawals is another good example, which was in Capella.
取款是另一个很好的例子，是卡佩拉。
I owned that feature, and I was responsible for making sure
我拥有该功能，我负责确保
that everything was running OK.
一切正常。
But there was another person on the team
但是团队中还有另一个人
that helped me through some things,
这帮助我完成了一些事情，
just so that we could deliver and be on time for the test net.
只是为了使我们可以准时进行测试网。
That's about it from team side of it.
从团队方面就这就是关于这一点。
We don't have a product owner at the moment per se.
目前，我们目前没有产品所有者。
We're mostly just managing it within the development team.
我们主要只是在开发团队中进行管理。
And we do have, because we have a Europe presence,
我们确实有，因为我们有欧洲的存在，
they tend to go to the all core dev schools
他们倾向于去所有核心开发学校
and I tend to be asleep in my bed at that time
当时我倾向于在床上睡觉
because it's 2 a.m. our time.
因为现在是凌晨2点。
That's about all I was going to look at
这就是我要看的
from the EIP kind of perspective,
从EIP的角度来看，
and I'm hoping people find that useful.
我希望人们发现这有用。
If there's no further questions,
如果没有其他问题，
I do have a quick performance thing that we could run through
我确实有一个可以经历的快速性能
or we could wrap it up there.
或者我们可以将其包裹在那里。
I'm easy either way.
无论哪种方式，我都很容易。
Thank you so much, Paul.
保罗，非常感谢。
It's also very interesting to see how it works within the team.
看到它在团队中的工作方式也很有趣。
It's an interesting insight.
这是一个有趣的见解。
Let's see if there are any questions about the AAP process.
让我们看看是否对AAP过程有任何疑问。
So far, we don't have any.
到目前为止，我们没有。
But it's very interesting.
但这很有趣。
so much because we've been using it as an example of how the changes implementation
这么多，因为我们一直在使用它来说明如何更改实现
things is done in the Ethereum that there is some EIP idea which goes through some
在以太坊中，有一些EIP想法经历了一些
research process then it's implemented and it's great to dive into that to
研究过程已经实施，很高兴深入研究
zoom in on how it's actually happening so it's really helpful yeah and let's see if
放大它实际发生的方式，所以它确实很有帮助，让我们看看是否是否
um we have we have any related questions otherwise i'm very glad to have to continue to give you more
嗯，我们有任何相关问题，否则我很高兴能继续为您提供更多
space and we have like maybe 20 minutes left it's okay with you at first um so we can we can use
空间，我们大概剩下20分钟，您一开始就可以了，所以我们可以使用
that time um somebody's typing so i just want to see if there's a relevant question and yeah no
那个时候有人打字了，所以我只想看看是否有一个相关的问题，是的
problem okay uh unrelated question but still uh whether um you are working on
问题好吧，嗯
implementation or any research related to epbs technically maybe similar to epbs not currently
实施或与EPB有关的任何研究在技术上可能类似于EPB
um i'm trying to follow the conversation on epbs it's very long um yeah and if anyone is interested
嗯，我正在尝试关注EPB上的对话，这很长，是的，如果有人有兴趣
There's an ETH R&D channel for EPBS.
EPB有一个ETH R＆D频道。
It'll be interesting to see how it pans out at the moment.
看到它目前如何抛弃会很有趣。
I don't think it's looking like it's going to be in Electra.
我认为它看起来不会在伊莱克特拉（Electra）。
But there's a lot of considerations to be had.
但是要有很多考虑。
Yeah, interesting. Thank you.
是的，很有趣。谢谢。
Any more questions?
还有其他问题吗？
Okay, I think we can go on.
好吧，我认为我们可以继续。
If you have more content, just feel free to continue.
如果您有更多内容，请随时继续。
Okay.
好的。
I was going to mention just a quick performance example.
我只提到一个快速的性能示例。
I'm sure this is potentially language specific,
我确定这是特定于语言的，
so sorry for anyone that doesn't look at Java,
很抱歉任何不看爪哇的人，
but Java has synchronized functions,
但是Java具有同步功能，
and synchronized functions basically run as a single process,
并同步函数基本上作为一个过程运行，
so only one can run all the time.
因此，只有一个人可以一直运行。
When I was looking at performance on Holsky, one of the things that I did was I tried to scale up
当我在霍尔斯基（Holsky）上查看表演时，我所做的一件事就是试图扩大规模
what the machine was doing on Holsky until a point where it started breaking.
机器在霍尔斯基（Holsky）上所做的事情，直到它开始破裂为止。
It can be a useful indicator of performance when things are starting to go negative. So I
当事情开始呈阴性时，它可能是性能的有用指标。所以我
I started with 10,000 keys and that ran fine.
我从10,000个钥匙开始，这很好。
I upped it to 15,000 to 20,000.
我将其提高到15,000至20,000。
20,000 things started going a little bit south,
20,000件事开始有点南方
but I wasn't happy with that.
但是我对此不满意。
And I upped it to a single node to be running 30,000 keys,
我将其提高到一个节点以运行30,000个键，
which is very not ideal,
这不是理想的
but it did show an interesting pattern
但这确实显示了一个有趣的模式
where when we're doing our local slashing protection,
当我们在当地进行削减保护时，
we need to run these functions
我们需要运行这些功能
that maintain the slashing protection data
维护削减保护数据
to ensure that we can't be slashed.
为了确保我们不能被削减。
Those functions are actually synchronized.
这些功能实际上是同步的。
So we started hitting a bottleneck,
因此，我们开始打瓶颈，
not as much on Mason block,
在梅森街区不多，
more so on the attestations
关于证明的更多
because your validators on average,
因为您的验证器平均
you can look at one 32nd of your validators
您可以查看验证者的第32个
that you're running are testing in every slot.
您正在运行的是在每个插槽中测试。
So if I'm running 30,000 validators,
因此，如果我正在运行30,000个验证者，
that's quite a lot of validators
那是很多验证者
that end up testing each slot.
最终测试了每个插槽。
And each one of them have to write an update to a file,
他们每个人都必须为文件写一个更新，
which is fine.
很好。
It's a very small amount of data.
这是很少的数据。
but if it's a if it's a function where it's basically locked that across those
但是，如果是一个函数，基本上是锁定的功能
30 000 validators i can only check one elevator at a time it becomes quite a resource constraint
30,000个验证器我只能检查一个电梯，它变成了很大的资源约束
so there was a little tiny feature that was a little bit scary to do
因此，有一个很小的功能有点可怕
to basically remove that synchronized.
基本上要删除该同步。
If you look at it in, it's not a new solution, basically.
如果您看一下，它基本上不是一个新解决方案。
If you look at databases, relational databases,
如果您查看数据库，关系数据库，则
they initially started with a table-level locking scheme
他们最初是从桌级锁定方案开始的
and they eventually determined
他们最终确定
that row-level locking was a lot smarter.
该排级别的锁定要聪明很多。
Basically, this is similar to that
基本上，这类似于
in that I'm locking one validator.
因为我要锁定一个验证器。
So multiple validators can be accessed at once
因此可以一次访问多个验证器
for their slashing protection,
为了削减保护，
but one validator can only be updated
但是只能更新一个验证器
like in a single sequence.
就像单个序列一样。
So you end up needing a bunch of locking data
因此，您最终需要大量锁定数据
around that power data.
围绕该电源数据。
So I actually have a bunch of records
所以我实际上有很多记录
and the local splashing protection record
和当地的飞溅保护记录
ends up having its own lock.
最终有自己的锁。
But the net result of that
但是最终结果
was about a 15% increase
大约增加了15％
in our effectiveness on other stations.
在我们对其他电台的有效性。
So it's funny how
所以很有趣
sometimes one little design decision,
有时一个小设计决定，
which is okay at low levels,
在低水平上还可以，
it's not okay when things scale up.
当事情扩大时，这是不好的。
So I thought that was just maybe a fairly simple performance-related one
所以我认为这可能只是一个相当简单的表演
that we look at sometimes.
有时我们会看。
Another example that I don't have on the slide is
我在幻灯片上没有的另一个例子是
UN64s are a full-blown object in Tecu.
UN64是TECU中的一个成熟对象。
So when I was looking at reducing memory size,
因此，当我查看减少内存大小时，
I was trying things for weeks and weeks,
我尝试了数周和几周的事情，
And then I had a look in our memory analyzer,
然后我看了我们的内存分析仪，
and it turned out that we had millions and millions of objects
事实证明，我们有数百万个物体
that all said 32E, which was this Uint64.
都说32e，那就是这个Uint64。
So I could save several hundred meg
所以我可以节省数百兆
just by making a single static variable to have 32E value in,
仅通过使单个静态变量具有32e值，in
which still blows my mind when I think about it today.
当我今天考虑时，这仍然让我震惊。
So there's some interesting performance stuff that happens in the background when you're
因此，当您的背景中会发生一些有趣的表演事物
doing development.
做发展。
The only other slide I had, probably a timely question, how do I become a cordev?
我唯一的另一个幻灯片，可能是一个及时的问题，我如何成为科尔迪夫？
The number one thing that always answers this question for me is get involved.
始终为我回答这个问题的第一件事是参与其中。
assume that you're not in a place where you're able to help out because a lot of people can
假设您不在一个可以提供帮助的地方，因为很多人可以
help out more than they realize um so my advice would be to pick a project a good example person
帮助他们比他们意识到的更多，所以我的建议是选择一个好榜样的人
is potus who basically got into prison because he was implementing a feature that he wanted that no
Potus基本上是因为他实施了一项他想要的功能
else wanted to implement it so he taught himself how to do it and is now on a cordial team um
否则想实施它，所以他自学了如何做，现在就在一个亲切的团队中
but pick a project try to use it and familiar familiarize yourself with it uh if you did pick
但是选择一个项目尝试使用它，并熟悉自己熟悉，如果您选择了
techie obviously we've got the consensus discord in that there's two channels we've even created a
显然，我们已经达成了共识的不和谐，因为我们甚至创建了两个渠道
a techie contributors channel.
技术人员贡献者频道。
So shameless plug from our side, if you
如果您
do want to get involved, that's a channel
想要参与，这是一个频道
that you could be talking on if you need help finding things
如果您需要帮助找到东西，您可能会谈论
or if you need help understanding the code.
或者，如果您需要帮助了解代码。
We do have developers looking in there.
我们确实有开发人员在那里看。
Even Eth R&D is a really good place.
甚至ETH研发也是一个非常好的地方。
EPBS was mentioned before, and there
之前提到过EPB，那里
is a channel dedicated to EPBS.
是专门针对EPB的渠道。
So if you are interested in that, I would be joining that channel and trying to get your head around how things work.
因此，如果您对此感兴趣，我将加入该频道，并试图让您围绕事情的运作方式。
And also, a lot of teams have hiring pages.
而且，许多团队都有招聘页面。
Consensus hiring pages always there.
共识雇用页面始终在那里。
And I think we are hiring for cordevs at the moment.
而且我认为我们目前正在招聘Cordevs。
and this is just from me because sometimes I'm my worst enemy
这只是我的，因为有时候我是我最大的敌人
don't let yourself doubt anything that holds you back
不要让自己怀疑任何使您退缩的事情
that is everything I had
那就是我所拥有的一切
awesome thanks so much Paul
非常感谢保罗
yeah also for those of you still listening
是的，对于那些仍在听的人
yeah joining programs like this study group
是的，加入像这个研究小组这样的程序
as well as the protocol fellowship are great ways to
以及协议奖学金也是一个很好的方法
get a little bit more structure and guidance through your journey into core development,
通过进入核心发展的旅程，获得更多的结构和指导，
if that's a path that you'd like to take. That's a good point. Protocol Fellowship is
如果那是您想走的道路。这是一个很好的观点。协议奖学金是
really, really good. We have had a lot of good experiences with people from there as well. So
真的，真的很好。我们也与那里的人一起度过了很多良好的经验。所以
it's definitely worth mentioning for sure. Yeah, actually, I wanted to ask about that.
绝对值得一提。是的，实际上，我想问一下。
Maybe if you can give people some tips on their first-time contributions.
也许，如果您可以给人们一些有关他们的首次捐款的提示。
You had a good experience with a fellow from the EPF before,
您以前与EPF的家伙有良好的经验，
so maybe some things that you liked about their interactions
所以也许您喜欢他们的互动的某些事情
or how it works for people.
或它对人的工作原理。
I think I didn't actually have to do very much to specify the project
我认为我实际上并不需要做很多事情来指定该项目
that was worked on previously from that, because it was already predefined,
从那以前是这样做的，因为它已经是预定义的，
I think, by the gentleman that did the change, but
我认为，做了改变的绅士，但是
they were very interested in
他们对
LiteClient basically and wanted to implement LiteClient for TeKu.
诉状基本上是想为Teku实施诉讼。
I suggested that doing it properly rather than doing
我建议这样做正确而不是这样做
the whole thing as it as a shallow dive would be a better option.
作为浅水潜水，整个过程将是一个更好的选择。
So we ended up developing
所以我们最终发展了
actually, he's probably one of the recent people to go into the storage layer
实际上，他可能是最近进入存储层的人之一
because he had to change that a fair bit
因为他必须改变这一点
and was able to produce some of the endpoints for client.
并能够为客户生成一些终点。
But because we were doing it fully tested and product ready,
但是，由于我们已经对其进行了充分的测试和产品准备就绪，所以
we didn't get all the way across it.
我们没有一路跨过它。
So one day we will revisit it,
所以有一天我们会重新审视它，
but it was a good outcome for everyone, I think.
我认为这对每个人都是一个很好的结果。
And I think he got a lot out of it.
我认为他从中得到了很多。
Yeah, awesome.
是的，很棒。
And maybe you mentioned good first issues.
也许您提到了一个很好的第一个问题。
maybe some other things where people can contribute to or any like active
也许人们可以为其他人做出贡献或类似活跃的事情
research development areas where you know, Tecubesu or other ports might need help?
您知道的研究开发领域，Tecubesu或其他港口可能需要帮助？
In terms of ERP's, they're obviously documented as they go through and it
就ERP而言，他们显然在经历时被记录下来
These things are free for anyone to join.
这些东西是免费的。
So if people believe that they can contribute to an ERP,
因此，如果人们认为他们可以为ERP做出贡献，
they should definitely get involved,
他们绝对应该参与其中，
reach out to the people that are championing it
与那些拥护它的人接触
and try to become part of the process.
并尝试成为过程的一部分。
A lot of information is flowing all of the time,
很多信息一直在流动，
so the biggest challenge is finding where the information that you need lives.
因此，最大的挑战是找到您需要生命的信息。
And ETH R&D is an excellent resource for that.
ETH R＆D是为此的绝佳资源。
There's a consensus dev channel, and there's an all core devs channel.
有一个共识DEV频道，并且有一个全核Devs频道。
Fairly accepting of questions that are considered.
相当接受被考虑的问题。
I wouldn't go spamming them, but I definitely wouldn't feel afraid to ask a question.
我不会垃圾邮件，但我绝对不会害怕问一个问题。
They're a fairly open bunch overall.
他们总体上是一个相当开放的一堆。
uh this the erp channels obviously keeping up with awkward abs is
嗯，这显然与尴尬的腹肌保持相符
uh like the calls you can watch them back on youtube uh one some people's contribution is
呃，就像您可以在YouTube上看到他们的电话一样，一个人的贡献是
largely summarizing those calls so i know um ben edgington for a while was joining them
在很大程度上总结了这些电话，所以我知道Um Ben Edgington有一段时间加入了他们
and producing just like a bullet point summary of those calls,
就像这些电话的子弹点摘要一样，
which I used to really appreciate because I could read that
我以前非常感谢，因为我可以读
rather than watch the hour and a half back because I never see it.
而不是看一个半小时，因为我从未见过。
So people contribute in different ways.
因此，人们以不同的方式做出贡献。
Obviously, there's the other side of it where people's contributions
显然，它的另一面是人们的贡献
are more about airdrop farming, which isn't great, but yeah.
更多地是关于空光耕种的，这不是很好，但是是的。
Yeah, it is interesting.
是的，这很有趣。
world okay did you get a little spam uh prs or stuff like that for one up from one of
世界还好，您是否得到了一些垃圾邮件UH PR或类似的东西，因为
it beacon apis is the weird one the beacon apis channel seems to get a lot more spam than i would
它是信标API是怪异的信标API频道似乎比我要获得的垃圾邮件要多得多。
expect and um i'm one of the main admins on that so i see it probably see it more than sometimes
期待，嗯，我是那个主要的管理员之一，所以我看到它可能比有时更重要
but like things like people commenting or close prs and stuff i don't know what that gets you
但是，就像人们评论或关闭PR和其他东西之类的东西，我不知道会有什么
it must get you something because people do it a lot yeah right and it's time consuming for
它必须给您一些东西，因为人们会做很多事情，是的，这很耗时
the dev teams who already have very little time so i wouldn't suggest doing it great yeah uh yeah
那些已经有很少时间的开发团队，所以我不建议这样做很好，是的
i noticed it in some some what you said like old prs issues and just random comments and then like
我在您所说的某些内容中注意到了它，例如旧PRS问题，只是随机评论，然后喜欢
it's also kind of annoying on github to block them because you need to file a whole report and
在GitHub上也有点烦人来阻止它们，因为您需要提交整个报告，并且
it's it's just too long process yeah um yeah yeah yeah thank you paul um
是的，是的，是的，是的，是的，谢谢，保罗嗯
We had a bit more difficult question, and I'm not that familiar with Java, but I think
我们有一些更困难的问题，我对Java并不那么熟悉，但我认为
this is like a new feature in Java 21 using virtual threads, maybe whether who uses them
这就像使用虚拟线程在Java 21中的新功能，也许是谁使用它们
or whether you leverage the latest features.
还是您是否利用最新功能。
At the moment, we're on to Java 17, so we're not using any of the new features in Java
目前，我们进入Java 17，因此我们没有使用Java中的任何新功能
21.
21。
I actually really wanted to use records, which I believe is Java 17, but the problem is the
我真的真的想使用记录，我相信这是Java 17，但问题是
reality of how we do things versus how records want them done wasn't very intrusive to using
我们如何做事与记录如何完成的现实对使用并不是很干扰
them either.
他们要么。
So sometimes we do use new features, but it just depends on the way we're using things.
因此，有时我们会使用新功能，但这仅取决于我们使用事物的方式。
Like the new switch syntax in Java 17, we have started using it a fair bit, but other
就像Java 17中的新开关语法一样，我们已经开始使用它，但是其他
features like records, we haven't really touched.
像唱片之类的功能，我们并没有真正触摸。
Hopefully soon we'll start moving to Java 21, but we need to also be realistic about
希望很快我们将开始搬到Java 21，但我们还需要对
making people move just for moving sake.
使人们只是为了搬家。
So add Docker image changes first usually, because that's easy lift.
因此，添加Docker图像通常首先更改，因为这很容易提升。
Right, it can break the environment for many people, it's a big step.
是的，它可能会破坏许多人的环境，这是一大步。
Yeah it gets listed as breaking change.
是的，它被列为打破变化。
Right, folks any other questions feel free to ask, we have maybe a few more, one
是的，人们其他任何问题都可以问，我们还有一些
last question or so.
最后一个问题左右。
I'm not sure, Josh, do you have anything here?
我不确定，乔什，你在这里有什么吗？
I think we are out of the question pool already.
我认为我们已经没有问题池了。
Yeah, I don't think so.
是的，我不这么认为。
Just a big thanks to you, Paul, for taking us through TeKu and giving us a good overview
保罗，只要感谢您，带我们浏览了Teku并给我们一个很好的概述
of that code base and how it works.
该代码库及其工作原理。
You're very welcome.
您非常欢迎。
Yeah, thank you very much.
是的，非常感谢。
Yeah, I appreciate it.
是的，我很感激。
it was really great to see
看到真是太好了
especially such a
特别是这样
I would say kind of hot and interesting
我会说有点热有趣
EIP as MaxEB
EIP为Maxeb
it's very heavily discussed
非常讨论
people have opinions
人们有意见
want to include it so it was really great to
想包括它，所以真的很棒
actually see it in action
实际看到它在行动中
yeah thank you so much Paul and again
是的，非常感谢保罗，再次
huge thanks for
非常感谢
picking up for us
为我们接我们
and
和
hope you all had some rest today
希望大家今天休息
have a good day
祝你有美好的一天
no worries thank you very much for your time
不用担心非常感谢您的时间
So yeah, thanks a lot Paul, and we'll see you around.
是的，非常感谢Paul，我们将与您见面。
Paul Krugman, All right, thanks Paul.
保罗·克鲁格曼（Paul Krugman），好吧，谢谢保罗。
Paul Krugman, All right, have a good day everyone.
保罗·克鲁格曼（Paul Krugman），好吧，大家都有美好的一天。
Paul Krugman, And to the rest of the study group, we will see you all in a couple
保罗·克鲁格曼（Paul Krugman），在研究小组的其他成员中，我们将在一对夫妇中见到大家
of days on Wednesday for a chat with Barnum, Bay, and Manon on MEB and censorship.
星期三的几天与Barnum，Bay和Manon聊天，并在MEB和审查制度上聊天。
Paul Krugman, Awesome.
保罗·克鲁格曼（Paul Krugman），很棒。
Paul Krugman, All right, thanks.
保罗·克鲁格曼（Paul Krugman），好吧，谢谢。
Paul Krugman, Thank you so much for following everyone.
保罗·克鲁格曼（Paul Krugman），非常感谢您关注所有人。
Thanks, Paul. Bye-bye.
谢谢，保罗。再见。
Thank you.
谢谢。
.
。